（忆往昔）
月光下化身成一个凶残的杀人野兽
A freak animal killing machine by moonlight.
狼人很难对付的
I mean, werewolves are badass.
我们已经知道如何撂倒这些家伙了
We already know how to bring these suckers down.
给他们心脏来颗银弹
One of these bad boys right to the heart.
我确实出了些问题 非常不对劲 我需要帮助
There's something wrong with me, really wrong. I need help.
- 你每天睡多久 - 不睡
- How much do you sleep? - I don't.
完全不睡吗
At all?
- 他的灵魂 不见了 - 那在哪儿呢
- It's his soul. It's gone. - So, where is it?
应该还在封印米迦勒和路西法的牢笼里
Still in the cage with Michael and Lucifer.
那该死的是什么东西
What the hell was that thing?
- 那也许是个始祖 - 始祖 就像
- It may have been an alpha. - An alpha? Like …
也就是那些怪物的祖先
The first one who spawned all the others.
这里面学问可多着呢
There's tons of lore about it.
给我捕猎去
Bring me creatures.
越是食物链的顶端越好
Aim high on the food chain, please.
- 我们可不是你的娇娃 - 绝对是
- We ain't your employees. - Of course you are!
你不过是个在十字路口晃悠的恶魔
You're nothing but a punk-ass crossroads demon.
那是曾经了
Was a punk-ass crossroads demon.
如今 已是地狱之王了
Now? King of hell.
我只需动动手指 就能让萨姆的灵魂归位
I snap my fingers, Sam gets his soul back.
否则我就再把萨姆推回那个牢笼里
Or I shove Sam right back in the hole.
（如今）
他吃了吗
Did he eat?
已经给他洗过澡了 对吗
You gave him a bath, right?
（布法罗 纽约州）
那么 你有带他去公园吗
Well, did you take him to the park?
那他嘘嘘和便便了吗
And did he make pee-pee and poo-poo?
很好
Good.
告诉他爹地爱他
Tell him Daddy loves him.
马上就回家
Be home soon.
什么鬼…
What the…
[邪恶力量 第6季第8集]
（肥佬的肋骨小屋）
我知道 鲍比 但肯定还有别的办法吧
I know, Bobby, but there's got to be another way.
我不知道 继续查呗
I don't know. Keep digging.
如果克劳力认为我们会…
I mean, if Crowley thinks we're just gonna …
克劳力认为你们会怎样啊 迪恩
Crowley thinks you're just gonna what, Dean?
是鲍比·辛格吗
Is that Bobby Singer?
帮我亲他一口
Give him a kiss for me.
我一会儿再打给你
I'll call you back.
好消息 小伙子们
Good news, boys!
我有份儿差事交给你们
I've got a job for you.
好话不说第二遍
I'm gonna say this once.
带着你的差事给我见鬼去吧
You can take your job and shove it up your ass.
这就是你跟自己老板说话的态度么
Is that any way to talk to your boss?
少给我装老大 蠢货
You're not my boss, dickbag.
迪恩啊迪恩 早说过了 别傲娇了
Dean, Dean. Been through this. Quit clutching your pearls.
你已经为我工作一段时间了 萨姆就更长了
You've been working for me for some time now. Sam here, longer.
我们当初又不知道
We didn't know.
知不知道对你来说有啥区别么
Like that makes a difference to you.
你现在根本是为达目的
You'd sell your brother for a dollar right now.
就可以不管你老哥的死活
if you really needed a soda.
- 听着 我想派你们… - 不干
- Look, I'm sending you - No.
你说什么
Beg pardon?
我是做过一些见不得人的事
I've done some shady stuff in my time,
但我不会干这个
but I am not doing this.
不干
No.
十英镑赌你会同意
10 quid says you will.
你喜欢痛感吗 萨姆 你喜欢地狱吗
You like pain, Sam? You like hell?
你别以为这事儿还有商量的余地
You need to stop thinking of this as some kind of deal.
现在我说了算 没的商量 你个傲慢的臭东西
This is a hostage situation, you arrogant little thug.
你老弟的命在我手上 搞清楚了吗
I own your brother! Do you understand me?
行了 迪恩 笑笑
Come on, Dean, smile.
也没那么糟
It's not that bad.
给你点儿犒劳吧
Here's incentive …
只要你抓一个活的始祖给我
You bag me a live alpha,
我答应你会双手奉还小萨萨的灵魂
and I'll give you little Sammy's soul back, with a cherry on top.
怎么 吸血鬼始祖还不能满足你吗
What, alpha vamp not good enough for you?
你最好别插嘴得好 除非你不想活了
Best mind where you poke your nose, if you want to keep it.
你俩愉快的猎捕旅程从这儿开始
Your merry little hike up the food chain starts here.
一个商人死在自己车里
Businessman found dead in his car …
胸部被刨开 心脏不见了
Chest ripped open, heart missing.
- 听起来像什么呢 - 狼人
- Sounds like? - Werewolf.
不 这不是满月日
No, it's not a full moon.
狼人都是在满月之时变身 真凹凸
Werewolves turning on the full moon … so '09.
他说得对
He's right.
六个月前的半月日 我和萨穆埃尔杀过一个
Samuel and I ganked one about six months back on the half-moon.
看来这种不正常情况已经持续一段时间了
Things have been out of whack for a while now, I guess.
是啊 我想也是
Yeah, I guess.
那么 就这么定了吧
So, it's settled then.
你们去猎捕那狼人 把它给咱带回来
You bag the howler, bring it home to papa.
回见了 帅小伙子们
See you soon, boys.
受害人还真是事业有成
So, the vic's a real class act.
即拥有一大批的廉价公寓
Owned a bunch of slum-grade apartments.
也有些独立式房屋
Couple houses, too.
就这样了吗 你就打算这么做了
So this is it? This is … this is what you're gonna do?
我做什么啊
What am I doing?
克劳力 他一直把我们玩弄于股掌
Crowley. He's so far up our asses.
我们想甩都甩不掉他
we're … we're … we're coughing sulfur,
但你 你居然就开始研究起这案子了
but you … you're just gonna work the case?
嗯 他掐住了我们的命门
Well, he's got us by the short and curlies.
我们还能怎么办
What else are we supposed to do?
只是… 老弟 我
It's just … you know, man, I…
我现在是在帮恶魔干活儿
I'm working for a demon now.
我甚至不知道你究竟是谁
I don't even know who you are.
我只不过
I just…
我只是需要点儿时间来消化下
I just need a second to adjust.
听着 这确实是个糟糕的局面
Look…This is a crap situation.
我懂的
I get it.
但是迪恩 我还是我
But, Dean, I am still me …
同样的大脑 同样的记忆
same melon, same memories.
我喜欢的音乐也没变
I-I still like the same music.
我还想着苏西·海泽
I still think about Suzie Heizer.
生物课上那个苏西·海泽
Biology class Suzie Heizer?
这能怪我吗
Can you blame me?
我知道你不信任我
Look, I know you don't trust me.
我做的一切也覆水难收
And I can't take back what I did.
但是我会证明给你看
But I'm going to prove it to you.
我依然是你弟弟
I'm still your brother.
你好 我们是霍尔特和威尔逊探员
How you doing? Agents Holt and Wilson.
联调局的
Feds?
对
Yeah.
联邦调查员来这里做什么
What are the feds doing here?
我们是特派专员
Oh, we're specialists.
专门被指派来回答那些
They call us in to answer the questions.
喜欢多管闲事儿的人提出的问题
of mouth-breathing dick monkeys.
你要给我们详细讲解下吗
So, you gonna walk us through this,
或者
or, uh…
他是码头工人
Dock worker.
上早班的工人发现了他
Guy on the morning shift found him …
胸腔被撕裂
chest ripped wide open.
和车里那具尸体一样吗
Same as the body in the car?
对 两天之内出现了两具尸体
Yeah, second one in two days.
两具尸体的内脏都不见了吗
Internal organs missing on both vics?
比如说心脏
Like their hearts?
好像是的
Uh…Looks like it, yeah.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
这人 他有什么仇人吗
So, this guy, he … he have any enemies?
对 树敌很多 但是
Yeah, plenty, but, uh,
我觉得他不可能和
I don't think it was a wolf or possibly a cougar.
狼或者豹子发生冲突吧
that had a beef with the guy.
你们应该明白吧 这只是动物袭击罢了
You do realize these were animal attacks?
动物怎么会来这里
An animal out here.
你觉得它是跑来坐船的吗
What, you think it came for the sailing?
早安
Morning.
你没睡觉
You didn't sleep.
因为你不用睡觉
'cause you don't…sleep.
对
Right.
是啊 真是一点都不惊悚啊
Yeah. That's not creepy at all.
我也没办法啊
Not like I can help it.
你就那么躺着看着我吗
So, you gonna just lay there staring at me,
要不要听听我的发现
or you want to hear what I dug up?
好吧
All right.
我们知道狼人
So, we know that werewolves.
大多数天性残忍狂躁 对吧
are basically id gone wild, right?
他们憎恨谁 就会在变身后把谁干掉
I mean, whoever they hate, they kill when they wolf out.
我一直在找受害者之间的联系
So, I've been playing connect the victims.
有何发现
And?
我想我找到了他们的共同点
And I think I found a common denominator.
来吧
So come on. Uh…
动作快点儿
Get the lead out, huh?
机器战警 等我穿好衣服先
Let me get dressed, robocop.
有什么可以效劳的
Yes, can I help you?
卡尔·哥瑞肯在家吗
Is Cal Garrigan at home?
我们有些问题想问问他
We've got a few questions we'd like to ask him.
在家 请进
Yeah. Um, come in.
亲爱的
Honey, um,
你去自己房间玩一会儿行吗
why don't you go play in your room for a little while, okay?
抱歉 有点乱
Excuse the mess.
请坐
Please sit.
两位喝点什么
Um…Can I get you guys anything?
不了 谢谢
No, thank you.
卡尔是你男朋友对吗
Um, so Cal is your boyfriend?
对
That's right.
他在哪里
And where is he?
还在睡吧 我想
Uh, sleeping, I think.
你可以叫醒他吗 他有客来访
You mind telling him up and at 'em? He's got some guests.
好 好 没问题
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
卡尔
Cal…
旺财 嘘
Lucky, shh!
他们是探员
These are agents…
霍尔特和威尔逊 早安 吧
Holt and Wilson. Morning…Ish.
你们好
Hey.
有何贵干
What's this?
你昨晚很晚才回家吗 卡尔
You out late last night, Cal?
就是 和朋友喝了几杯啤酒
Just, uh, you know, a couple beers with friends.
喝了几杯
How many's a couple?
我不知道 三杯 最多四杯
I don't know. Three, four tops.
既然你就喝了点儿啤酒
If all you had was beer,
为什么你满身伏特加的味道
then how come you're sweating vodka?
而且我猜你是穿着那些衣服睡觉的吧
And looks to me like you slept in those clothes. Am I right?
我不知道 可能吧
I don't know. I-I guess.
那你的意思就是
So what you're saying is,
你喝得烂醉 不省人事
you got blind drunk, you blacked out.
这好像不是第一次了吧
Something tells me this isn't the first time.
卡尔 说老实话
So, Cal, truthfully,
鬼知道你晚上究竟去了哪里
who knows what you've really been up to at night?
你们到底想怎样啊
Look, what's this about?
我们在调查罗纳德·哥瑞肯被杀的案子
We're investigating the death of Ronald Garrigan.
我哥哥
My brother?
请节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss.
我以为是动物袭击之类的
Yeah, I thought that was some kind of animal attack.
你们兄弟俩关系不太好吧
No love lost between the two of you, huh?
我们是有不同之处
Look, we had our differences, I guess.
我当然爱我的哥哥 但是
You love your brother, of course, but…
罗纳德有很多问题
Ron had a lot of problems.
他情绪很不稳定
He was, uh, volatile.
上次他来你家 你还报警了
Last time he was here, you called the cops?
对 他喝得烂醉 跑到我家来
Yeah, look, he came in here all messed up,
他还大吼大叫
and he was yelling.
他还对曼迪动手 所以我就报警了
He shoved Mandy. So, yeah, I called the cops.
我不知道这和他的死有什么关系
I don't see how that has to do with …
你的房东这周死了
Your landlord was found dead this week.
你知道吗
Were you aware of that?
报纸上登了 怎么了
Saw it in the papers. Why?
你们俩欠了好几个月的房租
Well, you two were pretty far behind on your rent, right?
他下了逐客令 是吗
He had sent eviction papers?
抱歉
I-I'm sorry.
房东是动物攻击致死
That was an animal attack.
巧的很啊 他俩都是因此丧命的
Funny enough, yeah … both of 'em were.
很巧 是啊 伙计们
So, great, great. Yeah, guys.
但他们的死干我鸟事
What in the hell do you think I had to do with 'em?
我们只是按规矩办事
Just following procedure.
不得不来问问
Had to ask.
祝你们今天愉快
You two have a good day.
卡尔很爱玩儿啊
So, Cal's a prince.
是啊 他连自己昨晚身在何处都糊里糊涂的
Yeah, doesn't even know where he was last night.
现在就去搞定他吗
Bag him now?
不 咱们得先搞清楚
No. We make sure.
没开玩笑吧
Really?
在把他交到恶魔手里各种受虐之前
Before we hand him over to a lifetime of demon rape?
我们当然要搞清楚
Yeah, really.
老天 卡尔还真是喝个不停
Boy, Cal just doesn't know when to quit.
三家小酒吧 一家脱衣舞俱乐部
Three scuzzy bars, one scuzzy strip club,
一根大麻烟卷 外加七八杯睡前安神酒
a chili-dog joint, seven or eight nightcaps,
现在又在仓库里狂饮威士忌
and now… scotches in the library.
看着我就觉得自己会得肝硬化了
I'm getting cirrhosis just watching this.
除了这些 我们一点成果都没有
Other than that, we got squat.
别心急
Let's just see.
哥们 天亮了
Dude, sun's up.
这家伙还是没变形
This guy's still on two legs.
理论上来讲
In theory.
他不会狼变了
He ain't wolfing out.
今晚是没戏了
Well, not tonight, anyway.
咱们撤吧
Let's head back.
晚些时候再来
We can re-attack this in a couple hours.
回见 哥们儿
Catch you later, man.
旺财
Lucky.
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doing?
不
No!
救命啊
旺财 好了
Lucky, that's enough.
卡尔
Cal?!
死性不改
Typical.
旺财
Oh, Lucky.
老实说
Honestly.
你是我唯一正经的男友了
You are the only decent boyfriend I have ever had.
我来大胆预测一下 看来不是卡尔干的
I'm gonna go out on a limb and say that it's not Cal.
绝妙的推理 福尔摩斯
Masterful deduction, Sherlock.
狼人怎么会在大白天袭击人类呢
I mean, a werewolf attack in daylight?
这事简直太诡异了
This whole thing is just weird.
猫狗大混居（《捉鬼敢死队》中经典台词） 乱成一团了
Dogs and cats living together … mass hysteria.
你应该清楚
So, you know this means.
我们现在只有一个嫌疑人了 对吧
that we're down to one suspect, right?
对
I know.
所有受害者都和曼迪有关
I mean, Mandy is right at the deep end of the vic pool.
你能搞定么
Can you do it?
什么
Do what?
把她塞进后备箱 交给克劳力
Shove her in the trunk, serve her up to Crowley.
萨姆 我能搞定
Yeah, Sam, I can do it.
宝贝 还烧么
You still feeling hot, baby?
喝点果汁 能好受一点
Here, have some juice. Make you feel better.
好的
Okay?
看
Hey, see?
旺财真贴心 知道你不舒服
Lucky knows you're not feeling well,
他想让你开心一点
and he wants you to feel better.
他很爱你 对吧
He loves you, doesn't he?
乖 真乖
There's a good boy.
乖狗狗
- 他很喜欢吱吱的声音 - 恩
- He loves a squeak. - Yeah.
腿断了
The leg broke off.
旺财 看你干的好事
Lucky, look what you did!
打扰你看新闻了吗
What, am I interrupting the morning show?
来吧 咱们出去转转
Come on. Let's go for a walk.
这是血迹吗
Hey, is that blood?
你又把小鸟咬死了是吧
Have you killed a bird again?
坏狗狗
Bad dog!
好的 没问题
Okay, okay.
- 那回见了 - 拜拜
- See you later. - Bye. Bye-bye.
女士
Ma'am?
探员们
Agents.
有何贵干
What are you doing here?
没人通知你吗
Nobody called you?
通知我什么
Called me about what?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真不敢相信
I just can't believe it.
我很遗憾
I'm really very sorry.
女士 我知道 现在可能不太合适
Ma'am, I know this isn't the best time,
但我们希望您能跟我们走一趟
but we'd like you to come with us.
为什么 你们觉得这是我干的吗
Why? You think I have something to do with this?
是我害了卡尔
With Cal?
当然不是
Of course not.
我们想问您一些问题 一些细节而已
We just got a few questions … I's and t's, mostly.
我
I, uh…
我们能改天再谈吗
Could we do it later?
我恐怕不行
I'm afraid not.
我的小孩感冒了 折腾了一晚上
My s… my kid has the flu, um, and he was up all night, so …
你跟我们走之后
Well, is there a neighbor or a friend.
能找邻居或者朋友帮忙看孩子么
who can watch him while you're gone?
抱歉 您说您儿子昨天一夜没睡对吗
I'm sorry. You said your boy was up all night?
是的
Uh, yeah.
你一直和他在一起吗
Were you with him all night?
我中间可能睡了半个小时吧
Well, I had, um, half an hour of sleep, maybe.
- 我能和您儿子谈谈吗 - 谈什么
- Can I talk to your son? - Why?
霍尔特探员 还有什么好谈的呢
Yeah, what difference does that make, Agent Holt?
相信我 这很重要
Trust me. It's important.
可以吗
Please?
不是她
Well, it wasn't her.
这可说不定
You don't know that.
她有不在场证据
She's got an alibi.
她在撒谎
She's lying.
你听到那孩子作证了 老弟 她没撒谎
You heard the kid, dude. She's not lying.
就算是 她还是有时间变身的 迪恩
Fine. She still had time to wolf out, Dean.
上次那狼人还跟我一起在床上呢
The last werewolf was in bed, with me,
还不是变身行凶去了
And she wolfed out.
不是针对你
Don't make this personal.
我想说的是
Look, all I'm saying is.
这件事 还有那些白天攻击人类的事
that between this and the daylight attacks,
怎么都解释不通
something's not adding up.
不查清原委
I'm not just gonna hand.
我是不会把她交给克劳利的
her over to Crowley until we figure out what.
你明白吗
You understand?
好 好 我明白
Okay. Okay. I understand.
不如你去看看卡尔的死亡现场
How 'bout you go check out Cal's crime scene,
看我们有没有遗漏线索
see if we're missing anything.
我回去监视阿曼达
I'll come back and keep an eye on Amanda.
不如你去 我留下吧
How 'bout you go and I'll stay here?
迪恩 我还没到不知道怎样工作的份上
Dean, I still know how to do my job.
我只是看着她 仅此而已
I'm just gonna watch her. That's all.
相信我
Trust me.
没事了 乖
You ok, boy.
快去急救站
Gotta find a aid.
快点
Hurry.
喂
Hey!
等下 等等 先生
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, wait! Mister!
先生 那是我的狗
Hey, mister, wait! That's my dog!
我的狗
That's my dog.
（莉莎）
喂
Hey.
喂 是我
Hey, man, it's me.
我这啥也没有
Well, I got bupkes here.
我有收获
I definitely got something.
起码 肯定不是狼人
It ain't a werewolf, for one.
哦 那是什么
Yeah, what is it?
剥皮行者
Skinwalker.
A skinwalker?
怎讲
As in…
就是说 他们家那狗该阉了
As in, the family dog seriously needs a neuter.
哇哦
Wow.
好多年没见过剥皮行者了
I haven't of a skinwalker in years.
对这概念有点儿生疏
I'm actually a little rusty on the profile.
我也一样
You and me both.
我刚找鲍比了解了一下
Uh, I just got the low down from Bobby.
他们可以随时随地变身
They can change anywhere, anytime.
只要被咬上一口就会被传染
Skinwalkers infect you with a single bite.
其他方面他们就像狼人的表亲
Otherwise, they're basically a werewolf cousin …
惧怕银器 嗜人心如狗粮
Silver will drop 'em, they chow hearts like snausages.
你遇上了啥情况 抓到他了吗
So what happened? Did you catch him?
还没有 不过我大概知道他会在哪里了
Not exactly. But I have some idea where he might be.
（瑞县宠物医院）
旺财你好
Hiya, Lucky.
坏狗狗
Bad dog.
先说要紧的
First thing's first.
看到了吗 银弹
you see this? This is silver.
别说我没警告过你
Don't say I didn't warn you.
好了 该走了
Okay, time to go.
你看 你是要吃敬酒
Now, we can either do this the easy way … hmm?
还是吃罚酒
or the hard way.
咋了 不管有没有灵魂 这招都很搞笑
What? Soul or not, that's funny.
这么跟你说吧 旺财
Well, I got to tell you, Lucky,
你难住我们了
You got us stumped.
为什么跟那家人住一起
I mean, why shack up with the family?
某种变态爱好吗
Is it a kinky thing?
你喜欢玩弄食物是吗
Do you like to play with your food?
旺财 打个滚 说话呀
Roll over, Lucky. Speak.
下地狱吧
Go to hell.
去过了 不适应
Already been. Didn't agree with me.
不如这样 我拿这把银刀
So, look, how about I take this silver knife,
给你修修形状 教你学乖些
and start carving some dog until you behave?
你想怎样就来吧
You do what you got to do.
萨姆 慢着
Hang on, Sam.
你不需要告诉我为啥跟那家人在一起
Listen, you don't have to tell me why you're with the family.
我知道
I get it.
你又知道了
Oh, you do, do you?
你杀了所有威胁到他们的人
You killed every threat that came near them.
你关心他们
You care about them,
以你那种愚不可及的方式
in your own whack-a-doodle kind of way.
很明显的
It's obvious.
我想要知道的是
What I want to know is,
那个跟你说话的人是谁
who was that guy you were kibitzing with?
他也是剥皮行者吗
He a skinwalker, too?
我不能说
Look, I can't say anything.
如果你不说 那女人和小男孩
But if you don't, then you're gonna put.
就会因你而有危险
the girl and the little boy in danger.
早晚有一天 这些麻烦事会找上他们
And sooner or later, all this crap is gonna come for them.
听着 我们才不在乎你死活
Now, look, we don't give a rat's ass about you.
我们想救的是他们
We want to help them.
这就是我们的立场
That's our angle. That's it.
对 那家伙是
Yeah, that guy, he's a…
跟我一样的什么东西
whatever it is I am.
他不是唯一一个
And he's not the only one.
你们有多少人
How many are you?
大概三十
About 30.
我们都是 都算是被征召的
We were all … we were kind of recruited.
征召
Recruited?
对 我当时流落街头
Yeah. Me, I was living on the streets.
他们找到了我
They found me.
告诉我说 只要咬一小口
They told me one small bite,
我就能变得又快又强
I'd be strong, I'd be fast.
给人当跟屁虫 还真是很大的进步啊
Sniffing people's butts? Yeah, that's a real step up.
对我来说的确如此
Well, it was for me.
你们那个史酷比小帮派在哪儿
Where is this little Scooby gang of yours?
无所不在
Everywhere.
我们在外面寻找合适的家庭
We're out there finding families,
一旦他们收留了我们 我们就「潜伏」下来
and once they take us in, we lay low.
「潜伏」 什么意思
"Lay low"? What the hell's that mean?
- 我们会等待一个命令 - 什么命令
- Well, we're waiting for the word. - What word?
一旦稳定下来 我们就会收到信号
Once we're settled, we get the signal…
然后我们就会袭击收留我们的家庭
…and we all turn on our families.
我们会在一夜之间转化他们
We change them, all in one night.
于是30个就会变成150个
30 becomes 150.
老天 你们就像「潜伏」的癌细胞
God, you're a sleeper cell.
这么说也对
Yeah, well, that's one way to say it.
那么 发出命令的是谁
So you're waiting for word from who?
你们的头儿是谁
Who organized you?
有个兽群领袖
There's a pack leader.
你们的始祖
Your Alpha?
始祖是什么
What's an Alpha?
你们的第一个剥皮行者 最强壮的那个
The … the first skinwalker, the strongest.
他的确很强壮
Well, he's plenty strong,
但我不觉得他是什么始祖
but, no, I-I don't think so.
我知道别的镇上也有这种家伙
I'm pretty sure there's guys like him in other towns.
我们可不是唯一的一群
We're not the only pack out there.
很好 那你可以帮我们阻止这家伙
Fantastic. Then you can help us stop him.
不不 我做不到
Oh, no, I can't. No.
你做得到
Yes, you can.
不 你们没明白 没人做得到
No, you guys don't get it. No one can.
把我转化的那些家伙 他们非常残忍
These guys who turned me … they're ruthless.
萨姆 别闹了
Sam, not helping.
捡回来 混蛋
Fetch this, dick.
听我说
Listen to me.
说真的 你准备对那家人做些什么
What are you gonna do to that family, really?
你要撕裂那小男孩的喉咙吗
You gonna put your jaws around that little boy's throat?
把他压在身下 听着他对妈妈哭嚎吗
Clamp down, listen to him cry for his mom?
可我猜
'cause I'm gonna guess.
他俩是你这悲惨的一生中
that these are the only people who in your pathetic life.
唯一对你好的人了吧
have ever showed you any kindness.
所以 你要么就那样干
So it's either that…
要么就帮助我们阻止这一切
or you can help us stop it.
所以…
So…
我们怎么才能接近一群
How are we supposed to get near something.
一百码外就能闻到我们气味的家伙呢
that can smell us 100 yards off?
不用接近
We don't.
兽群领袖
The pack leader.
我们要把他干掉吗
We're taking him down?
没错 你有更好的主意吗
Yeah. Got a better idea?
没有 我…
No, I…
如果这样的话 克劳力可能会不高兴
Crowley's not gonna be too happy about that.
谁鸟他高不高兴
Who gives a rat's ass?
我让那家伙多活一秒
We let that thing live one second,
它就会给那群疯狗发出信号 那就…
and it sends out that psychic dog whistle and pchew!
可另一方面 它也能带我们找到他们的始祖
On the other hand, it could lead us to an Alpha.
那克劳力就能把我的灵魂还回来了
Then Crowley would give me my soul back.
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
150个人类被变成怪物 这就是你想要的
150 people turned into monsters. That's what you want?
不 当然不是 我…
No. Of course not. I…
我只是问问
I'm just asking.
够了 你知道吗 就这样吧
All right, you know what? That's it.
什么
What?
你说你是个老实人 对吗
You say you're "Just folks, " Yeah?
你喜欢棒球啊苹果派啊什么的
That … that you like baseball and apple pie or whatever.
但事实上 我不知道你是什么
But truth is, I don't know what you are.
- 反正你不是萨姆 - 迪恩 拜托
- 'cause you're not Sam. - Dean, come on.
我是说 你的大块头
I mean, it's your gigantor body and …
也许连大脑都是萨姆的
and maybe your brain,
但你不是
But it's not you.
所以你就别装了
So just…stop pretending.
就算帮咱俩的忙吧
Do us both a favor.
他看起来很紧张 对吗
He looks nervous, right?
换你你不紧张
Wouldn't you be?
换我 我会出卖我们
I'd double-cross us.
他可能会想到 如果还想活下去
I mean, he's got to realize that's his best bet,
出卖我们就是他最好的选择
if he wants to keep breathing.
不 他会坚持到底的
Nah, he'll go through with it.
你是说 因为他爱那家人
You mean 'cause he loves that family?
没错
Yeah.
换我 我还是会出卖我们
I'd double-cross us.
谢你吉言 你可真会安慰人
Thanks, dexter. That's reassuring.
我只是想聊点什么
Just making conversation.
开始了
Here we go.
那个大个子 那个司机
That big guy, the driver …
旺财在公园见的就是他
That's the guy Lucky met in the park.
老大出来了
And there's el jefe.
把他干掉
Take him out.
旁边有人
It's not clean.
我们要确保一击毙命
We got one shot at this … literally.
快开枪
Take the shot.
我正在努力
I'm trying!
- 她挡住我了 - 别管了 快开枪
- She's in the way. - Take it anyway!
来吧来吧来吧
Come on, come on, come on. Ahh.
现在咋办 备用计划吗
So, plan "B"?
咱有备用计划吗
We've got one?
求求你们 不管你们想要什么
Please, whatever you want.
求你们放过我儿子吧
Just please let my son go.
听着 伙计 现在我也无能为力了
Look, man, there's nothing I can do.
老大很生气
The boss is pissed.
你根本未经许可
These murders that you've been doing?
就杀了那些人
You didn't ask for permission!
你会毁掉我们整个计划的
Now you're gonna screw up the whole damn plan.
- 我警告过你了 - 我知道 对不起
- I tried to warn you. - I know. I'm sorry.
这 这肯定有点误会
There … there's been a mistake.
我们跟这事完全没关系
T-This has got nothing to do with us.
这完全就是因你而起 大姐
It has everything to do with you, sister.
总之 你还是不是我们一伙的
So, you with us or not?
是 当然是
Yes, of course I am.
那好 证明给我看
Fine. Prove it.
转化他们 就现在
Turn them. Now.
两个都要 让我们亲眼看看
Both of 'em, while we watch,
否则我就把你们都杀了
Or I'll kill you all.
哦天呐…
Oh, my…
什么气味
What is that?
- 妈妈 - 别怕
- Mommy! - It's okay.
曼迪 过来 跟我来
Mandy! Come on, come on.
你是谁 我根本不认识你
Who are you?! I don't even know you!
我们认识的 相信我 我是来帮你们的
Yes, you do. Trust me, I'm trying to help.
快 快
Come on, come on!
快进去
Get in there.
- 但我不… - 快进去
- But I don't … - Get in there!
锁好 锁好
Bolt it! Bolt it!
这边 宝贝 躲在下面
Here, baby, go under here.
好了 呆在那儿 宝贝 你会没事的
Okay, stay there, honey. You'll be safe.
你在保护他们
You're protecting them?
我为你做了这么多
After what I did for you?
我给了你再活一次的机会
I gave you your life back!
而他们呢
them?
你对他们来说一文不值
You're nothing to them.
你就是条狗
You're a dog.
我 我本来只想转化他们
I-I was gonna turn them.
但现在 我要杀了他们
But now I'm gonna kill 'em.
旺财
Lucky?!
你以为我会跟你来场狗之间的较量
So you think this is gonna be a dogfight?
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea.
银弹 旺财
Silver bullet, Lucky.
就说一句
One.
我不是要来打扰你们的
I'm not here to bother you.
我只是… 我只想说一件事
I just…Uh, I just want to say one thing.
你和艾丹…
You and Aidan…
你们是我唯一的亲人
You're the only family I ever had.
我知道…
And I know …
我知道这听起来… 我知道…
I know that sounds … I know…
我知道我是什么
I know what I am.
只是…
It…
只是从没有人对我那么好过
It's just that no one has ever been so nice to me before,
因此…
So…
谢谢了
So, thank you.
离这屋子远点儿
Get away from this house,
你这个疯子
You psycho.
如果你
And if you ever,
再接近我和我的儿子
Ever come near me or my son again,
我发誓…
So help me…
我知道我活该…
I know I probably deserve…
狗在我眼里永远不会跟以前一样了
I'll never look at a dog the Same.
不过还真难说啊
Makes you wonder, though, huh?
什么难说
What?
到底还有多少狗群
How many packs are out there.
如果它们都在等命令呢
What if they're all just waiting for the signal, you know?
我在想
So…I was thinking.
你是对的
You were right.
什么事
About?
我不是你弟弟
I'm not your brother.
我不是萨姆
I'm not Sam.
好
Okay.
那些什么「我还是原来的我」
All that "Blah, blah, blah, " About being the old me?
都是废话
Crap.
就拿莉莎和本来说
Like Lisa and Ben, right?
我一直装作在乎他们
I've been acting like I care about them.
可我不在乎 一点也不
But I don't. I couldn't care less.
这些会让我感觉好受些么
Is this supposed to make me feel better?
你想要个真实的我 这就是
You wanted the real me. This is it.
我并不在乎他们
I don't care about them.
我甚至都不真的在乎你
I don't even really care about you.
只是…
Except that…
我真的需要你的帮助
I need your help.
如果我不直截了当跟你明说的话
And you're clearly not gonna stick around for much longer.
你明显就快忍不下去了 所以…
Unless I give it to you straight, so…
我的确做过许多坏事 比你想的还坏
I've done a lot worse than you know.
我在猎魔的过程中杀过无辜的人们
I've killed innocent people in the line of duty.
但我确信
But I'm pretty sure.
这不是以前的我会做的事
It's not something the old me could've done.
或许我应该有罪恶感
And maybe I should feel guilty.
但我没有
But I don't.
萨姆 说重点
Sam, get to the punch line.
我不知道这样的我
I don't know if how I am.
到底是好是坏
Is better or worse.
这感觉很不一样
It's different.
完成了任务 却感觉不到任何伤痛
You get the job done, and nothing really hurts.
这也不算是最糟糕的
That's not the worst thing.
但我在想
But I've been thinking.
曾经的萨姆都不是这样的
I was that other Sam for a long time.
我记得…
And it was…
做那样的萨姆很痛苦
It was kinda harder.
但我同样记得 做那样的萨姆…
But there are also things about it I remember that I…
总之这么说吧
Let's just say.
也许我还是该重新变回原来的萨姆
I think I should probably go back to being him.
有意思
That's very interesting.
你迈出了一大步
It's a step.
那么
So?
我们做我们该做的
We do what we got to do.
我们去把我弟弟找回来
And we get my brother back.